《迷失》前情提要
Previously on "lost"...
女士们先生们  大洋航空815航班的幸存者
Ladies and gentlemen, the survivors of oceanic 8-1-5.
我刚杀了个
I just killed a man who's been perched...
上个礼拜在这地方外蹲点的男人
Outside this facility for the last week.
我要你跟我到一个安全的地方来
I want you to come with me somewhere safe.
你和我有点共同的兴趣
You and I have common interests.
不是只有我们离开了这个岛
We're not the only ones who left the island.
-我们  我们不应该离开  -再见  Jack
- We... were not supposed to leave. - bye, jack.
我们得回去  Kate
We have to go back, kate.
他有没有告诉你我离岛了
Did he tell you that I was off the island?
是的  他说了  他说我必须回去
Yes, he did. he said that I had to come back.
我们也要把他带走的
We're gonna have to bring him, too.
宝宝醒了
Ah. mm. baby's awake.
轮到你了
It's your turn.
早上好  给你  博士
Morning. here you go, doc.
我不需要台词
I don't need a script.
我们开始吧  我很忙的
Let's go. I don't have all day.
-快点  -好
- Speed.  - okay.
达摩组织二号录像
Dharma orientation film number two,
第一次
Take one.
开始
And... action.
大家好  我是Marvin Candle博士
Hello. I'm dr. marvin candle,
这是我们箭头站的...
And this is the orientation film for station two,
第二号录像片
The arrow.
鉴于你对这个具体领域的专业知识
Given your specific area of expertise
对于建立这个站的目的
You should find it no surprise
你应该不会感到惊讶
That this station's primary purpose
这个站是为了研发自卫策略
Is to develop defensive strategies
以及收集情报的
And gather intelligence
主要是针对岛上的敌对土著
On the island's hostile indigenous population--
张博士
Dr chang!
-张博士  -你干嘛
- Dr. chang?  - damn it! what the hell?!
-停  -先生  兰花站出了点事
- Cut!  - sir, we got a problem down at the orchid.
在那边
Over here.
我们正以你要求的规格削减岩石
We were cutting through the rock, right on your specs.
那时钻头融化了
That's when the drill melted.
-钻头融化了  -是的是的
- The drill melted?  - yeah, yeah.
还有3米就到原计划的界限了
3 meters from the margin line on the plans.
我们用了6个碳钻头
We went through six carbon drill bits,
最后一个直接就被烤烂了
And the last one just fried.then my operator
然后我的工程师就开始发疯了
My operator Starts grabbing his head and freaking out.
我们给墙拍了声纳图像
We sonar-imaged the wall.
墙里大概有一个20米的空心处
There's an open chamber about 20 meters in,
就在岩石后面
Behind the rock.
有什么东西
There's something in there.
唯一进去的办法
And the only way to get to it
是在这里和这里放炸药
Is to lay charges here and here
炸开...
And blast through it and take a look
绝对不允许
under no circumstances.
这个站建在这里的原因就是
This station is being built here because of its proximity
它距离我们确信的无穷的能源相当接近
To what we believe to be an almost limitless energy.
那种能源  如果我们正确使用
And that energy, once we can harness it correctly?
我们甚至可以扭曲时间
It's going to allow us to manipulate time.
是
Right.
好吧  那又怎样  我们可以回去杀了希特勒了
Okay, sohat? we're gonna go back and kill hitler?
别傻了
Don't be absurd.
这都是有规则的
There are rules,
不能破坏的规则
Rules that can't be broken.
那你想让我做什么
So what do you want me to do?
你什么都别做
You're gonna do nothing.
如果你再继续挖掘哪怕就一厘米
If you drill even 1 centimeter further,
那能源都可能被释放
You risk releasing that energy.
那是你希望发生的么
Is that you want to happen?
上帝保佑我们
God help us all.
好吧  把他弄上去  我们走
All right, get him up. let's go.
看着点路
Watch yourself!
对不起  先生  不会再这样了
Sorry, sir. it won't happen again.
好吧  我来...
All right. I'll grab the rest of his stuff.
你听到了吗
Did you hear that?
时空旅行  那家伙以为我们有多蠢
Time travel.how stupid does that guy think we are?
我们走  伙计们
Let's go, guys.
■
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视原创翻译制作
最新最快的美剧 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译： Buffy小朋友  小帝  Daisy静  zerk
翻译： 牛牛  blackeyepea 字幕总监：lonelyatta  梁良
■
时间轴： 虎牙 校对：  许愿
为什么你不把这盖上  Jack
Why don't you close that up now, jack?
来,我们把他带回车里  该走了
Come on. Let's get him in the van. it's out back.
我们要把它带到哪去
Where are we taking him?
一旦我们接上Hugo  再考虑这个
We'll worry about that once we pick up hugo.
Hurley...
他被关在一个精神病院里
Is locked away in a mental institution.
招募他比
Which should make recruiting him
你其他朋友都简单了
Considerably easier than the rest of your friends.
他们已经不是我朋友了
They're not my friends anymore.
就是这种精神
Oh, that's the spirit.
我们怎么到这来的
How did we get here?
这些都是怎么发生的
How did all this happen?
因为你们离开了  Jack
It happened because you left, jack.
我们开始吧  好么
Now let's get started, shall we?
那么接上Hurley之后...然后呢
So once we get hurley... then what?
然后我们去接Sun Sayid...
Then we get sun, sayid...
当然还有Kate
And Kate, of course.
我不觉得这样可行
I don't see that happening.
你最后一次见他是什么时候
When was the last time you saw him?
我是说Locke
I mean, Locke.
在岛上
On the island...
在兰花站的温室下面
In the orchid station below the greenhouse.
我向他道歉,是我把他的生活弄得一团糟
I told him I was sorry For making his life so miserable,
然后他就走了
And then he left.
显然John的来访对你影响很大
So obviously John's visit to you made an impression.
他说了些什么让你对他坚信不疑
What did he say to make you such a believer?
Sawyer  Juliet
Sawyer,Juliet,
船上的每个人  我们丢下的每个人
Everyone from the boat... and everyone we left behind--
John说要不是我回来  他们都会死
John said that they'd die, too, if I didn't come back.
他有没有告诉你岛移动之后那些人怎么了
Did he tell you what happened to them after the island moved?
没
No.
没  他没说
No, he didn't.
那我们永远不会知道了
Then I guess we'll never know.
三年前...
这到底是...
What the...
Richard  Richard
有人吗
Anyone?
出什么事了
What happened?
那道光是什么
What was that light?
我们一定在辐射范围内
We must've been inside the radius.
那道光到底是什么
What the hell was that?
我不知道
I don't know.
货轮怎么消失了
Where's the freighter?
-可能是沉了  -不可能
-Maybe it went down. -Unh-unh. No way.
刚刚那船还在冒黑烟
A minute ago, that boat was coughing black smoke.
现在就消失了
Now there's just nothin'?
那驾直升机呢
What about the helicopter?
刚才正在追那货轮
It was heading for that boat.
Rose
Rose!
-Bernard  -Rose
-Bernard! -Rose!
-看见Rose了吗  -没有
-Have you seen rose?! -No.
哦  天哪
Oh, my god!
-Bernard  -Rose
-Bernard! -Rose!
-你刚去哪了  -我刚在教堂那边
-Where were you? -I was over... by the church.
-那...那声响是怎么回事  还有那道光  -我不知道
-What was that sound?What was that light? -I don't know.
冷静点  不用发慌  好吗
Just calm down. There's no need to panic, all right?
-我们先回营地然后..
-We'll just go back to camp and...
-冷静,不用慌,我们不能回去了
-Calm down no need to panic?We can't go back to the camp.
-你说什么  -营地没了
-What the hell are you talking about?-There is no camp.
天空一道亮光  然后就成了这样
The--the sky lit up, a-and then this.
厨房  消失了
The--the kitchen?Gone.
然后那些帐篷  所有的水和食物  都消失了
And--and all the tents, all the food and water... gone.
除了我们剩下的都消失了  所有的东西
Well, everything but us. All of it.
都消失了
It's gone.
不是消失了
It's not gone.
Daniel
Daniel!
嘿
Hey.
我以为你在货船上
I thought you were on the freighter.
没  我们没能成功
No, we never made it.
刚才闪光的时候我们正在离开货轮
We were on our way out there when it happened.
你什么意思  营地不是消失了
What do you mean, the camp's not gone?
-你他妈的又是谁  -他是Dan
-Who the hell are you anyway? -That's dan.
-是我们的物理专家  -听着  我们没时间了
-He's our physicist.-Listen, we have no time.
我想让你带我去个人造的
I need you to take me to something man-made,
人工修建的地标建筑
Something that was built, any kind of a landmark.
在离这儿15分钟路程的地方有一个达摩站
There's a dharma station 15 minutes from here.
你是说那个我们炸掉了的舱口
You mean the hatch? The one we blew up?
太好了
That's perfect.
下一次到来之前我们需要赶紧行动了  好吗
We should get moving before it happens again, okay?
下一次什么到来之前
Before what happens again?
我们的营地怎么消失了
And why is our camp gone?
你们的营地不是消失了
Your camp isn't gone.
而是还没建成
It hasn't been built yet.
嘟嘟  进隧道了
Choo choo! Tunnel!
我觉得嘟嘟知道的更多
Oh, I think choo choo knows better than that.
他要钻进隧道  永不回头
He goes into that tunnel, he's never coming back out.
继续看卡通  宝宝
Watch your cartoons, Goober.
妈妈马上回来
Mommy'll be right back.
-Austen小姐吗  -什么事
-Ms. Austen? -Yes?
你好  我是Agostoni&Norton法律事务所的Dan Norton
Hi, I'm Dan Norton of the law firm Agostoni&Norton.
-我们能谈谈吗  -这位是
-May we have a moment of your time?-And who are you?
他是我的助手
He's my associate.
如果我能进去谈谈的话  我会很乐意解释一下...
If I could just come in, I'll be glad to explain--
不  你可以在这儿解释清楚
No, you can explain right here.
好吧  听你的
Okay, you got it.
Austen小姐  我们来是想取你和你儿子
Ms. Austen, we're here to get a blood sample from you
Aaron的血液样本
And one from your son Aaron.
我有法官授权的法院指令
Now I have a court order signed by a judge
按要求你看到此文件就要接受抽血
-For you to relinquish your blood upon being served these papers
-为什么  -以此确定你与孩子的关系
- Why?  - To determine your relationship to the child
抱歉  我不明白  谁是
I'm sorry. I don't understand. um, who's the--
我无权泄露客户身份
I'm not at liberty to divulge the identity of my client.
-你的客户  -请让我们进屋好吗
- Your client?  - please, may we come in?
-滚出我的房子  -如果你不合作
- Get off my property.  - if you won't comply,
那我恐怕就要请长官来了
Then I'm going to have to come back with the sheriff.
去请你的长官吧
Then come back with the sheriff.
妈妈你去哪里
Where you going, mommy?
宝贝  我们要去度假
We're going on vacation, baby.
宝贝  说再见
Say bye-bye, baby.
你为什么从直升机上跳下来
Why did you jump off that helicopter?
和你说过  我们没油了
I told you. we were runnin' out of gas.
我要确定她
I wanted to make sure she--
确定他们回到了船上
I wanted to make sure they got back to the boat.
-现在也无所谓了  不是吗  -抱歉
- Don't matter now anyway, does it?  - excuse me.
请你们二位务必跟上  多谢合作
I really need the two of you to pick up the pace. okanks.
别的先不说
First things first.
把你的上衣给我
Give me your shirt.
-我的上衣  -没错
- My shirt?  - yeah.
我可以肯定我们有更重要的事情要做
I really think we have far more pressing matters
比给你上衣更重要
Than me giving you a shirt.
-不如我们继续走吧
- How about we just keep moving, okay?
不如我们到此为止,来听听你解释下目前状况
how about we call a time-out, So you can tell us what the hell is going on?
-不如你相信我吧 -相信你吗
- how about you trust me? -Trust you?
-我根本不认识你  -我们真的没时间来解释
- I don't know you!  - We really do not have time for me to try to explain.
你不知道,要解释起来有多难
You have no idea how difficult that would be for me to try to explain
这现象对于量子物理学家,都很难说清
This--this phenomenon to a quantum physicist. That would be difficult,
所以让我来解释简直
So for me to try to explain whatever is happening--
天呐
Oi!
你在干嘛
What in bloody hell do you think you're doing?
闭嘴  小妹  否则你也挨一下
Shut it, ginger,or you're get one too
张嘴说话
Now talk.
这个岛
The island...
把这岛想象成
Think of the island
一张旋转着的唱片
Like a record spinning on a turntable...
可是它现在是跳转
Only now that record is skipping.
不管Ben linus在兰花站做了什么
Whatever Ben linus did down at the orchid station...
我想都已经
I think it may have
把我们隔离了
Dislodged us.
和什么隔离
Dislodged us from what?
时间
Time.
所以我们的营地没了
So that's why our camp is gone?
是因为这岛在穿越时光
Because the island is moving through time?
是的  可能是小岛  也可能是我们
Yeah, either the island is, or we are.
什么
What?
看起来好像是我们在穿越
And it's just as likely that we're moving,
你的人还有我们
Your people and us.
你组里的人都是你负责的  对吧
And everyone in your group-- you're all accounted for, right?
不是所有人
Not everyone.
Locke
Locke.
有人吗
Is anyone there?!
Hello?!
听见吗
不要
Hey!
啊
Uhh!
你是谁
Who are you?
-听着  听我说  -飞机上还有几个人
- Well, listen, listen  - how many others onboard?
你搞错了  我没坐那架飞机
You don't understand. I didn't come on that plane.
不老实
Wrong answer.
不  等等
No, wait! stop! stop!
我知道你  我认识你
I know you. I know who you are.
你的名字是
Your name...
你的名字是Ethan
Your name is ethan.
-你叫Ethan  -你是谁
- Your name is ethan.  - who are you?
我叫John Locke
My name is john locke.
我知道这会很难理解
I know this is gonna be hard to understand,
但是Ben Linus派我来做你的领导
But ben linus appointed me as your leader.
这是我听过最荒唐的事
That is the most ridiculous thing I've ever heard.
永别了  John Locke
Good-bye, john locke.
见鬼
Great.
我们现在什么时间  聪明鬼
So when are we now, whiz kid?
或者是在过去
We're either in the past...
或者是在未来
Or we're in the future.
去往巴黎的23号航班
flight 23 to paris
将在15号登机口登机
Will begin boarding at gate 15.
请准备好您的登机牌
Please have your boarding passes ready.
[法语]
(In french)
晚上好  女士  您今晚要去哪里
Evening, ma'am. where you flying to tonight?
洛杉矶
Los angeles.
好的  请出示您的护照
Of course. may I see your passport, please?
抱歉
Excuse me.
kwon小姐  您能稍候一下吗
Could you wait here for just one moment, ms. kwon?
喂  你去哪里
Hey! where are you going?
开门
Open this door.
把门打开
Open this door!
省省力气吧
Save your breath.
他们都听我的命令
They only do what I tell them to do.
是你
You.
是你带我来这里的吗
You had me brought in here?
为什么
Why?
你胆子够大的
You had the audacity
大庭广众之下顶撞我
To approach me in broad daylight
还是在我的合作伙伴面前
In front of my business associates... In public.
为什么带你来这里
Why did I have you brought here?
因为你太过无礼
Because you showed me no respect.
我是值得尊重的  sun
I will be respected, sun.
够吓人的了
Fair enough.
从你担心你的航班开始
Since you seem to be worried about your plane,
我放下了所有的工作
I'll get right down to business.
你提到我们...
You mentioned that you and I had...
都感兴趣的事
Common interests.
为什么不确切地告诉我是什么
Why don't you tell me exactly what they might be?
去杀Benjamin Linus
To kill benjamin linus.
受害者被枪杀于自己的车里
The victim was found shot in his car
在圣罗莎医院的私人心理健康中心
On the grounds of the santa rosa hospital,
位于洛杉矶郊外
A private mental health care facility outside los angeles. okay.
我们去找他
Let's go get him.
警察已认定凶手是
Police have now identified their suspect in the shooting
医院的一名病人
As a patient at the hospital
叫Hugo reyes  于傍晚早些时候逃出
Who escaped earlier this evening--hugo reyes.
是否觉得这个名字很熟悉
Now if that name sounds familiar to you,
他正是大洋六人组之一
That's because reyes was a member Of the infamous oceanic six.
至于为何他会谋杀一个造访者
As to why he may have murdered a visitor to the facility
并且在自己生活了两年的地方
Where reyes lived for two years,
仍然无从所知
That remains a complete mystery.
好吧...
Well...
看起来我们得换个方案
Looks like we have a change of plan.
她来了
Here she comes, right now.
这是你要的  先生
Here's your order, sir.
-不用找了  -谢谢
-Keep the change. -thank you.
爽
Awesome.
-来一块吗  -不用  谢谢
-You want a fry? -no, thank you.
可能你多吃点可口的食物,你就不会去外面杀人了
You know, maybe if you ate more comfort food You wouldn't have to go around shooting people.
老兄  你在圣罗莎外面搞定那个人  是谁
So that dude you popped outside santa rosa--who was he?
无所谓  他揣着武器在监视你
I don't care. he was armed and he was watching you.
他自找的
That made him an enemy.
你断定他是来杀我的吗
Do you think he was gonna kill me?
在Bentham死后  我不会再冒任何风险
I'm not taking any risks. after bentham died--
-你说的是locke吗  -嗯  就是locke
-You mean locke. -Yes, I mean locke.
我也需要一个那么酷的代号
I need a cool code name.
什么时候变得这么敏感了
So when'd you become so paranoid?
如果你这两年
If you'd spent the last two years
经历过我所经历的
Doing the things I was doing,
你也会和我一样敏感
You'd be paranoid, too.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
对什么敏感
Paranoid? like what?
什么样的经历
What kind of things?
我曾为Benjamin Linus做事
I was working for benjamin linus.
等等  他现在是我们一伙的吗
Wait. he's on our side now?
听我说  Hurley
Listen to me, hurley.
如果你不幸遇见他
If you ever have the misfortune of running into him,
无论他说什么  反着去做就行了
Whatever he tells you, just do the opposite.
等在这里
Wait here.
-他还好吗  -不知道
-Is he all right? -I don't know.
还有呼吸么
Is he breathing or what? who is that? check him out.
小心  那家伙有枪  快跑  报警
Look out! that guy's got a gun! run! get out of here! call the cops!
Hurry
Hurry!
Sayid
Sayid!
还好吗
You okay?
把我弄上车
Get me to the car.
老兄
Dude. dude.
啊  天呐
Oh, man.
我想这里应该是安全的
I thought it was supposed to be a safe house.
看来不应该离开岛上
I never should've left the island.
嘿  你觉得他在找我们吗
Hey, do you think he's looking for us?
你说谁
Who?
Widmore
Widmore.
他花了20年才发现这个地方
It took him, like, 20 years to find this place the first time.
我要集中精神了
I'll start holding my breath now.
来这里
Over here!
-这就是那个舱吗  -以前是
-Is this the hatch? -it was.
爆炸了  跟我们离开时一样
Blown up, just like we left it.
好吧
Okay.
那么现在的时间是...
So when we are now...
在你们坠机后
It's now after you and your people crashed on the island.
-我们的帐篷又回到海滩了吗  -有可能
-You sayin' our camp is back on the beach again? -it's possible, yeah.
-好  我要回去  -嘿  别
-Good. I'm going back. -hey. no, no.
-没意思  -盯着这个洞更没意思
-It's pointless. -more pointless than staring at a hole in the ground?
谁知道下一次闪光会是什么时候
We don't know when the next flash is coming.
当你回到海滩的时候,帐篷可能会又消失了
By the time you get back to the beach, The camp could be gone again. yeah,
-要是没有消失呢
-but what if it ain't?
要是现在直升机还没起飞呢
Hell, what if the helicopter hasn't even taken off yet?
我们可以警告他们
We could warn them
阻止他们飞向那条船上
Stop them from ever flying to that boat.
不是这么回事
That's not the way it works.
谁说的
Who says?
你什么都不能改变  不能
You cannot change anything. you can't.
无论你做什么都是徒劳无功
Even if you tried to, it wouldn't work,
为什么
Why not?
时间就好比一条街道
Time--it's like a street, all right?
在街道上我们可以向前走  可以掉头向后走
We can move forward on that street, we can move in reverse,
但是我们永远不能制造出一条新的街道
But we cannot ever create a new street.
如果试图改变这些
If we try to do anything different,
无论怎样都会失败
We will fail every time.
无论发生了什么
Whatever happened, happened.
你怎么知道这么多  小子
How do you know so much about this, danny boy?
我知道这些是因为
I know about this because...
我花费了毕生精力学习空间学
I've spent my entire adult life studying space-time.
我知道这些是因为
I know all this because
这本日记包含了我学习
This journal contains everything I've ever learned
所有关于达摩组织的内容
About the dharma initiative.
这就是我在这的原因
This is why I'm here.
我知道发生了什么
I know what's happening.
那我们怎么才能让它停下来
So how can we stop it?
我们不能让它停下来
We can't stop it.
那谁能
Then who can?
Richard
Richard?
John
john
Richard...
发生什么事了
What is happening?
你会失血至死的
What's happening is that you're bleeding to death.
在这
Here.
我要把子弹取出来
I need to get the bullet out.
你怎么知道我的腿中弹了  Richard
How did you know there was a bullet in my leg, richard?
你告诉我的  John
Because you told me there was, john.
不  我没有
No, no. no, I didn't.
你会的
Well... you will.
是Ethan开枪打的我
It was ethan who shot me.
善有善报  恶有恶报
What comes around, goes around.
我在什么时间
When am i?
John  时间是相对的
Well, john, that--that's all relative.
慢点  慢点
Wait, wait.
噪声  天空光芒四射的时候  你在哪
The--the noise, when the sky lit up... where did you go?
我哪都没去  John  是你离开了
I didn't go anywhere, john. you went.
好的  这里受伤了
All right, this--this is gonna hurt.
如果你继续动伤口会恶化  别动
It'll be a lot worse if you move, okay? hold still.
好了
Uhh! all done.
老天
Jeez.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你怎么知道我在这的
How--how did you know that I was here?
你怎么知道在哪能找到我  我想解释  John
How did you know where to find me? I wish I had time to explain it, john.
但是你马上要移动了
But you're gonna be moving on soon,
这之前我要重申两件事  "移动"
And we need to go over a couple of things before you do. "moving on"? aah!
对不起  第一件事
Sorry. the first thing, okay?
你要清理伤口,每两小时一次
You're gonna need to clean out the wound Every couple of hours
体重尽量放在另一条腿上
And keep as much weight off the g as you can, all right?
小岛会处理其他的事  但是我没
The island'll do the rest, john, all right? but I don't--
第二  不不  集中精神
Second thing-- no, no, pay attention.
下次我们在见面时  我就不认识你了
Next time we see each other, I'm not gonna recognize you.
-明白吗  你把这个给我
All right? you give me this. all right?
这是什么
What is this?
-指南针  -干什么用
It's a compass. what does it do?
指向南方  John
It points north, john.
我希望有更多时间解释这些
Look, I wish I had time to be more sensitive about this
但是要接受的事  实在太多了
Because it's a lot to swallow,
你必须知道这些才能完成你的使命,
But you need to know it in order to do what you gotta do.
继续刚才说的
So I'm just gonna say it, okay?
救这座岛唯一的办法
The only way to save the island
-就是把你们中离开的人带回这里  -Jack  Kate
Is to get your people back here--the ones who left. jack, kate...
直升机撞到了船  那条船
The chopper was headed for the boat. the boat--
不  他们没事  他们已经回家了
No, they're fine, john, and they're already home,
所以你必须说服他们回来
So you have to convince them to come back.
我该怎么做
How--how am I supposed to do that?
你会死  John
You're gonna have to die, john.
那么  你们把它炸了之前那是什么
So... what was this thing before you guys blew it up?
-达摩站  -干什么的
A dharma station. for what?
有一个叫Desmond的人住在里面
There was a man named desmond living down in it.
每108分钟他就会按一次按钮
He was pushing a button every 108 minutes
拯救世界
To save the world.
真的
Really?
是的  真的
Yeah. really.
妈...
Son of a...
...的
Bitch.
这个舱  它回来了
The hatch--it's back.
我猜你还没找到它
I guess you haven't found it yet.
你去哪
Hey! where you goin'?
后门  我去找点生活用品
Back door. I'm gettin' some supplies.
James  等等  这不是好主意
James, wait. not a good idea.
天空能在一瞬间变成它想成为的东西
The sky can flash all it wants,
但我可不想重新开始Dilbert
But I ain't startin' over, dilbert.
我不要钻木取火
I ain't rubbin' two sticks together and making a fire,
我不要狩猎野猪
And I ain't huntin' damn boar!
那有食物  啤酒和衣服
There's dharma food, beer and clothing in there.
不管怎样  我都要让Desmond让我进去
And I'm gettin' desmond to let me in one way or another.
不会成功的  朋友
That's not gonna work, my friend.
-为什么  -因为他刚出来的时候
-why not?  -because desmond didn't know you
还不认识你
When he first came out of there.
那意味着你没有遇到  也意味着你不能遇到
That means you've never met, which means you can't meet.
如果我听你的话  那非常有吸引力
Th would all be fascinating if I was listening to ya.
你怎么知道Desmond在那里呢
So how you do know desmond is even in there?
里面可能是任何人
Think about it. it could be anybody.
我不在乎谁在那里
I don't care who's in there.
等会
Wait.
-等会  -打开这该死的门
-Wait. -open the damn door!
-不管用了  -会管用的
-It won't work. -sure it will.
开门  这是未来的圣诞节鬼魂
Yo, open up! it's the ghost of christmas future!
没人会来开门的
No one--no one is gonna answer.
开门  打开这个该死的门  开门
open! open the damn door! open the door!
你在浪费时间
You're wasting your time.
开门  我知道你能听到
open up! I know you can hear me.
如果没有发生  那就不可能发生的
If it didn't happen, it can't happen.
-打开这该死的门  -James你不能改变过去的
-Open the damn door! -you can't change the past, james!
我在意的每个人都在你那该死的船上被炸死了
Everybody I care about just blew up on your damn boat.
我知道我不能改变什么
I know what I can't change.
我们应该回到海滩上
We should get back to the beach.
今天很累了
It's been a long day.
如果没有什么值得回去的话
Why are we going back to the beach
那我们还回沙滩干嘛
If there's nothing to go back to?
那你留在这吧
So stay here.
那妞喜欢我
That chick likes me.
怎么了
What?
Wh-- what? what's the matter?
你
You...
我从来就没流过鼻血
Ugh. I haven't had a nosebleed since I was little.
Dan我没事的
Dan, I'm fine.
是的是的  你没事的
Yeah. no, no, no, you're-- um, of course you're fine.
你知道么  流鼻血是征兆
I'm, uh... you know, the sight of blood is,..
是的,是好事,你是物理学家  对吗  我们走吧
Yeah, well, it's a good thing You're a physicist then, isn't it? shall we?
是的  我的包
Yeah, um... my pack.
我把我的包落在舱门了,我最好去拿回来
Of course I left my pack back at the hatch crater. I better get it.
你和别人一起回去吧
Why don't you head back with everyone else?
-我会跟上的  -别犹豫了
-And I'll be right behind you. -don't dillydally.
没关系
I wouldn't think of it.
拜托开门吧
Please let this work.
拜托请开门吧
Please, please, please, let this work.
-不要开枪  -你最好解释一下
-Don't shoot. -then you'd best explain
干嘛一直敲我的门
Why you've been bangin' on my door
都敲了20分钟了  兄弟
For the last 20 minutes, brother.
Desmond
Desmond.
是你吗
Are you him?
他  是谁
"him"? who?
我的接班人
My replacement.
不  我不是
No, I'm not.
我不是
I'm not. I'm not. I'm...
我认识你吗
Do I know you?
是的  某种程度上
Yeah... in a way.
但你听着  这不重要
But listen, that's not important.
Desmond什么才重要  我正要和你说
What is important, desmond, is what I'm about to say to you.
你得听我说
I need you to listen.
Desmond你是唯一能帮我们的人
You're the only person who can help us because, desmond...
规则
The rules...
规则并不适合你  你是特殊的
The rules don't apply to you. you're special.
你是唯一而且特别的
You're uniquely and miraculously special.
你到底在说什么
What are you talking about?
好的  听我说  听着
Okay, listen to me. listen!
如果那架直升机成功降落在岛上
If the helicopter somehow made it off the island,
如果你回家了
If you got home--
什么直升机  你在说什么
What helicopter? what are you talking about?
听着  你得听我说  否则有人就会死了
listen, I need you to listen, or people are gonna die.
我叫Daniel Faraday  现在
My name is daniel faraday, and right now
被你们丢下的人们
Me and everyone else you left behind--
我们很危险
We're in serious danger.
你是唯一能帮我们的了  我需要你
You're the only person who can help us. I need you
回到牛津大学  回到我们相遇的地方
To go back to oxford university. go back to where we met.
我要你去找我母亲  她叫
I need you to go there and find my mother. her name is--
你还好吧
Are you all right?
我在岛上
I was on the island.
你离开那岛有3年了
You've been off the island for three years now.
你现在很安全
You're safe now.
那只是个梦
It was just a dream.
Pen那不是梦
It wasn't a dream, pen.
那是记忆
It was a memory.
Desmond  你要去哪
Desmond, where are you going?
Des
Des?
Desmond
Desmond?
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
我们走
We're leaving.
去哪
Leaving to go where?
牛津大学
Oxford.